Register of the Frank McAdams Albrecht Papers, 1928-1965
Hoover Institution Archives
- Correspondence, 1943-1945. (Box No. 3-8.)
  - McFarland, Clay (Fort Sam Houston, Texas), 1950
  - McGarr, Major General Lionel C. (Fort Leavenworth), 1956
  - McGinley, Major General Eugene (Washington, D.C.), 1954
  - McNutt, Colonel Charles H., 1955
  - Magruder, Lieutenant General Carter B. (Washington, D.C.), 1957, 1959
  - Maloney, Major Robert A., 1956-1957
  - Mann, James F. (Rome, Georgia), 1959
  - Mann, Mrs. James, F., Sr. (Rome, Georgia), 1959
  - Marks, Brigadier General Edwin H., 1946, 1954
  - Martin, Major General Joseph I., 1948, 1954
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology (Cambridge, Massachusetts), 1949
  - Massingale, Lieutenant Colonel John Thomas, 1947
  - Mathenson, Lieutenant Colonel John D., 1943, 1960
  - Mathews, Lieutenant Colonel H. W., 1945
  - Maurel, Lieutenant Colonel Pierre (Orleans, France), 1952-1953
  - Maverick-Clarke (San Antonio, Texas), 1954
  - Medaris, Major General John B., 1957-1958
  - Melitta-Werke Bentz & Sohn (Minden, West Germany), 1956
  - Meloy, Major General G. S., Jr. (Washington, D.C.), 1958
  - Melton, Major General Robert B. (Brooklyn, New York), 1958
  - Meyer, Colonel Carl W., 1955
  - Meyer, Brigadier General Richard D. (Washington, D.C.), 1957-1958
  - Meyers, Major General Colby M., 1954
  - Mielenz, Colonel Lloyd E. (Macon, Georgia), 1947
  - Military Engineer, The (Washington, D.C.), 1951, 1955
  - Miller, Lieutenant Colonel James M., 1957
  - Mills, Colonel William H., 1955
  - Milton, Hugh M., II (Washington, D.C.), 1957, 1960
  - Mingledorff, C. S. (Atlanta, Georgia), 1958
  - Mingledorff, W. Lee, Jr. (Savannah, Georgia), 1960
  - Minton, Major General A. M. (Washington, D.C.), 1960
  - Missildines Pharmacy (Tryon, North Carolina), 1954
  - Mitchell, Lieutenant Colonel Donald E., 1954
  - Moehlman, Lieutenant Colonel Arthur H., 1945-1947
  - Moffett, Colonel W. P. (Saint Paul, Minnesota), 1950
  - Moody, John L. (Los Angeles, California), 1955
  - Moody, Lester S. (Augusta, Georgia), 1957-1960
  - Moore, Major General Cecil R., 1943-1955
  - Moore, Major General Ned D. (Washington, D.C.), 1957
  - Moore, Vincent B., 1950, 1956-1957
  - Morgan, Lieutenant General Sir Frederick (Northwood, Middlesex, England), 1958
  - Morgan, Tom (West Point, Georgia), 1959
  - Morley, John D. (Wimbledon, England), 1942
  - Morton, Colonel William, 1955, 1957
  - Mount, Colonel Eric (Salisbury, England), 1944
  - Mueller, Ruth H. (San Antonio, Texas), 1946
  - Murphy, Lieutenant Colonel William F., 1958
  - Musgrove, Colonel A. M., Jr. (Washington, D.C.), 1960
  - Napier, Brigadier General C. S. (London, England), 1943 (Box 6.)
  - Neely, Frank H. (Atlanta, Georgia), 1957
  - Newman, Major General James B. (Winter Park, Florida), 1959
  - New York National Guard and Naval Militia State Armory, The Officers Corps (Buffalo, New York), 1957
  - Nold, Major General G. J., 1953
  - Norell, Brigadier General James A. (Washington, D.C.), 1959
  - Norman Hurst Limited (London, England), 1954
  - Norman, Robert C. (Atlanta, Georgia), 1960
  - Normandy, George M. (Atlanta, Georgia), 1957
  - North Dakota Water Users Association (Minot, North Dakota), 1960
  - O'Donnell, Colonel Edward J. (Washington, D.C.), 1958
  - Olmstead, Colonel Loren W., 1953-1955, 1960
  - O'Neill, Major General Edward J., 1955
  - O'Shea, John (New York, New York), 1957
  - Padgett, Lieutenant Colonel Wade H., Jr., (Brussels, Belgium), 1958
  - Page, Colonel R. J. B., 1951-1953, 1958-1959
  - Palm Beach, Florida, Mayor (Palm Beach County, Florida), 1960
  - Palmer, Lieutenant General Charles D. (San Francisco, California), 1957
  - Palmer, Lieutenant Colonel J. H. (Fort Sam Houston, Texas), 1950
  - Palmer, General W. B. (New York, New York), 1955, 1957
  - Parker, E. F. (Washington, D.C.), 1957
  - Parkin, Lieutenant Colonel C. M., Jr. (Fort Belvoir, Virginia), 1958
  - Parks, Major General F. L., 1953
  - Partridge, Major General R. C., 1954
  - Patterson, Governor John (Montgomery, Alabama), 1959
  - Paulus, Lieutenant Colonel E. C. (Langley Air Force Base, Virginia), 1955
  - Peacock, Ollie (Fort Pierce, Florida), 1960
  - Peacock, Richard A. (Birmingham, Alabama), 1958
  - Pence, Major General Arthur W., 1943, 1953-1954
  - Penguin Books, Ltd. (Middlesex, Great Britain), 1954
  - Penn Mutual Life Insurance Co. (Philadelphia, Pennsylvania), 1954-1956
  - Pennsylvania State University (University Park, Pennsylvania), 1956
  - Perception de St. Jean-de-Braye (St. Jean de Braye, Orleans-Loiret, France), 1954
  - Perpetuum-Ebner (St. Georgen, West Germany), 1956
  - Person, Brigadier General Jack L. (Washington, D.C.), 1957-1958
  - Petersen, Captain Robert J. (Fort McPherson, Georgia), 1959
  - Peterson, Major Gustave R. (Summit, New Jersey), 1948
  - Phi Kappa Psi, Pennsylvania State Univerity (University Park, Pennsylania), 1957
  - Philco Corporation (New York, New York), 1956
  - Phillips, John T. (Albany, Georgia), 1958, 1960
  - Phillips, John T., Sr. (Albany, Georgia), 1959
  - Pick, Lieutenant General Lewis A., 1951
  - Picknell, Colonel Milton O., 1956
  - Pierce, Captain J. B., 1945
  - Picknell, Colonel Milton O., 1956
  - Pierce, Captain J. B., 1945
  - Pierce, Major General James R. (Fort George C. Meade, Maryland), 1957
  - Pierce Brothers (Hollywood, California), 1955
  - Pine, Colonel Lynn W., 1955, 1957-1959
  - Plank, Colonel Ewart, G., 1943
  - Plath, John G. (Bismarck, North Dakota), 1950
  - Polk County, Department of County Welfare (Columbus, Ohio), 1956
  - Potter, Governor W. E. (Balboa Heights, Canal Zone), 1959
  - Potter, Brigadier General W. E. (Omaha, Nebraska), 1955
  - Potter, Colonel Seymour A., Jr. (Washington, D.C.), 1955
  - Powell, Lieutenant General Herbert B. (Fort McPherson, Georgia), 1960
  - Powers, Colonel William F., 1948, 1959, 1955, 1959
  - Prentiss, Major General Louis W., 1949, 1953, 1955, 1958
  - Preston, John, M.D. (Tryon, North Carolina), 1955
  - Pullan, Patricia, 1944, 1947, 1949
  - R.C.A. Manufacturing Company, Inc. (Camden, New Jersey), 1942
  - Ragusi, Anthony V. (Biloxi, Mississippi), 1960
  - Rahn, George J. (St. Paul, Minnesota), 1950
  - Rains, Albert (Washington, D.C.), 1960
  - Ramsey, Brigadier General Thomas H. (Brentwood, California), 1955
  - Ranck, Brigadier General Joseph R. (Forest Park, Georgia), 1957
  - Ravenhill, Brigadier General Colin, 1945
  - Ratner, Reuben, M.D. (Los Angeles, California), 1955
  - Rawls, O. G. (Jacksonville, Florida), 1960
  - Read, Charles D., Jr. (Atlanta, Georgia), 1960
  - Reader's Digest (Pleasantville, New York), 1955
  - Reber, Major General Miles (Washington, D.C.), 1948-1949, 1953
  - Redding, Lieutenant Colonel William D. (Fort Monroe, Virginia), 1956
  - Reeves, T. C. (Columbus, Georgia), 1957
  - Reighter, Major (Omaha, Nebraska), 1950
  - Reingburg, Colonel V. H. E. (Munich, Germany), 1945
  - Renfroe, Colonel D. J., 1945
  - Renshaw, Colonel Clarence (New York, New York), 1958
  - Republique Francaise, Presidence du Conseil. Secretariat General permanent de la Defense Nationale. (Paris, France), 1954
  - Rhett, Captain John T., 1955
  - Richardson, Bonnie (Mrs. J. Frank) (Tryon, North Carolina), 1955-1956
  - Riddick, Major John, 1960
  - Ristic, Major General V. Yugoslav People's Army, n.d.
  - Robert, Lawrence Wood, Jr. (Atlanta, Georgia), 1958-1960
  - Roberts, Lieutenant Colonel Charles M., 1954-1960
  - Roberts, Brigadier General J. T. (Washington, D.C.), 1956
  - Roberts, Mrs. Joe B. (Minneapolis, Minnesota), 1951
  - Roberts, Colonel Nathan J., 1953
  - Robinson, Major General Bernard L. (Washington, D.C.), 1958
  - Rockland Tackle Company (New York), 1954
  - Roper, Major General Harry McK. (Washington, D.C.), 1958
  - Rossig (Bonn, Germany), 1954
  - Rowland, Colonel Henry C., Jr., 1952-1960
  - Royal Automobile Club (Pall Mall, England), 1943
  - Ruffner, Lieutenant General Clark L. (Fort McPherson, Georgia), 1958, 1960
  - Rumaggi, Brigadier General Louis J. (Washington, D.C.), 1954
  - Rutledge, Major General Paul W. (Fort Bliss, Texas), 1955
  - Ryan, Major General C. E., 1956
  - Ryan, Chaplain (Major General) Patrick J. (Washington, D.C), 1957
  - Salter, Lieutenant Colonel Joel, 1944-1945
  - Saltzman, Evan (Bismarck, North Dakota), 1953-1955
  - Sanguinet, Major Edgar Y. (New Orleans, Louisiana), 1949
  - Saturday Evening Post (Philadelphia, Pennsylvania), 1954
  - Saunders, Harry H. (Fort St. Joe, Florida), 1959
  - Saunders, Peter (Aberdeen, Scotland), 1954
  - Schnell, Ray (Bismarck, North Dakota), 1951
  - Schomburg, Major General August, 1959-1960
  - Schuler, Oberforstmeister (Kassel, Germany), 1954
  - Scott, O. V. (Atlanta, Georgia), 1959
  - Seitz, Brigadier General J. F. R. (Langley Air Force Base, Virginia), 1955
  - Selden, Armistead I., Jr. (Washington, D.C.), 1960
  - Seybold, Colonel John S. (Bismarck, North Dakota), 1949
  - Shaffer, Lieutenant Colonel William K. (San Francisco, California), 1959
  - Shaugnessey, Colonel L. W. H., 1952
  - Shaw, Frank K. (Atlanta Georgia), 1960
  - Shepherd, Commodore James M. (Atlanta, Georgia), 1959
  - Shiely, J. L. (St. Paul, Minnesota), 1950
  - Shimonek, Captain Stewart (Corpus Christi, Texas), 1959
  - Shipe, Colonel B. H. (Fort Leavenworth, Kansas), 1956
  - Shoestring Construction Company (Dry Gulch, New Mexico), n.d.
  - Shotwell, John S. G. (Baltimore, Maryland), 1950
  - Sibley, Brigadier General Alden K., 1957-1960
  - Siebert, John W., Jr. (Pierre, South Dakota), 1953, 1958, 1960
  - Sikirica, Master Sergeant Stanley (Langley Air Force Base, Virginia), 1955
  - Sistovaris, J. A. et Ses Fils (Athens, Greece), 1954
  - Skillman, Lieutenant Colonel Charles S., 1953
  - Skinner, O. G., 1958-1959
  - Slaughter, Colonel Don F. (Washington, D.C.), 1954-1955
  - Smather, n.d. (Box 7.)
  - Smelser, 1st Lieutenant, Paul E., 1943
  - Smith, Reverend A. E. (Bismarck, North Dakota), 1952, 1954
  - Smith, Brigadier General C. Rodney (Washington, D.C.), 1954-1955
  - Smith, Donald V. (London, England), 1958
  - Smith, Reverend Theodore (Bismarck, North Dakota), 1958
  - Smoot, Rear Admiral Roland N. (Washington, D.C.), 1958
  - Smyser, Colonel R. E., Jr. (Fort Sam Houston, Texas), 1949-1950
  - Sneed, Reverend Wilson W. (Atlanta, Georgia), 1958, 1960
  - Snively, Dorothy M., 1950, 1953, 1955
  - Society of American Military Engineers (Norfolk, Virginia), 1955
  - Sollohub, Colonel Julian V. (St. Louis, Missouri), 1960
  - Sorley, Colonel M. E. (Atlanta, Georgia), 1946
  - Soule, Colonel John E., 1954
  - Spainhour, Carl M. (Washington, D.C), 1958
  - Sparks, Tommye (Mrs. Tom C.) (Houston, Texas), 1949
  - Speidel, Brigadier General George S. (New York, New York), 1958
  - Spies, Colonel G. H. (Fort Sam Houston, Texas), 1955-1956
  - Spring, Colonel S. G. (Canal Zone), 1959-1960
  - Spry, Lieutenant Colonel D. C., 1943
  - Staffa, Major Rudolph, 1956
  - Stafford, Fred O. (Los Angeles, California), 1952
  - Stevens, E. M. (San Antonio, Texas), 1947
  - Stevens, Colonel W. A. (Savannah, Georgia), 1960
  - Stewart, Major General George C. (Washington, D.C.), 1953
  - Stewart, Mildred (Mrs. C. W., Jr.) (Alexandria, Virginia), 1959
  - Stiemke, Robert E. (Atlanta, Georgia), 1960
  - Stone, Colonel Raymond, Jr. (West Point, New York), 1953
  - Stoner, Specialist 2 Ovie L. (Fort Dix, New Jersey), 1957
  - Storke, Major General Harry P., 1955
  - Stovall, Lieutenant Colonel Oran C. (Fort Sill, Oklahoma), 1947
  - Stover, Captain W. Harney (Philadelphia, Pennsylvania), 1956
  - Streit, Major General Paul H. (Washington, D.C.), 1949
  - Strong, Arthur D., 1945-1946, 1950-1951, 1959
  - Strong, Brigadier General Pascal N. (Cincinnati, Ohio), 1953
  - Sturgis, Lieutenant General Samuel D., Jr., 1949-1960
  - Sudgen, Major General Henry H. C., 1953-1960.
  - Svensson, Brigadier General Eric H. F. (Fort Stewart, Georgia), 1958
  - Swartz, Brigadier General Charles H., 1953
  - Sweany, Brigadier General Kenneth S., 1948, 1953
  - Sweely, Captain Joe W., 1956
  - Tailluer Fils & Cie. (Paris, France), 1953
  - Tandy, Colonel F. S. (Balboa Heights, Canal Zone, Panama,), 1949
  - Tate, Colonel F. J. (Washington, D.C.), 1955
  - Taton, Earl L. (Alexandria, Virginia), 1954
  - Taylor, Adrian (Bismarck, North Dakota), 1951
  - Taylor, General Maxwell D. (Washington, D.C.), 1959
  - Teale, Colonel Willis E. (Fort Belvoir, Virginia), 1946
  - Thacker, Clarence (Kissimmec, Florida), 1957
  - Thermal Belt Telephone Co. (Tryon, North Carolina), 1955
  - Thompson, Lieutenant Colonel Martin A., 1945
  - Thornycroft, Sir John (London, England), 1943
  - Threadgill, Lieutenant Colonel Walton O., 1953
  - Threadgill, (Mrs. Walton O.), 1953
  - Thurmond, Senator Strom (Washington, D.C.), 1960
  - Thwaite, Charles E., Jr. (Atlanta, Georgia), 1960
  - Tiernan, Chaplain (Colonel) L. Curtis, 1945
  - Towle, Colonel S. Woggie (Washington, D.C.), 1954
  - Townes, Brigadier General Morton E. (Washington, D.C.), 1958
  - Townsend, Lieutenant Colonel Clyde F. (Washington, D.C.), 1958
  - Trach, Colonel Bui Quang, 1960
  - Trout, Guy M. (Dallas, Texas), 1949
  - Troxler, Colonel Paul D. (Jacksonville, Florida), 1957-1960
  - Trudeau, Major General Arthur G. (San Francisco, California), 1953
  - Trulock, Lieutenant Colonel Sue B., 1946-1960
  - Tulley, Major General David H., 1952-1957
  - Uncles, Major General John G., 1955
  - United Clothing Company (Washington, D.C.), 1955
  - United Services Automobile Association (San Antonio, Texas), 1954
  - U.S. Army Department. The Adjutant General (Washington, D.C.), 1946-1948
  - U.S. Army, Europe. Communication Zone. Engineer Division, 1953
  - U.S. Army War College. The Commandant, 1957
  - U.S. Fourth Army. Engineer Section (Fort Sam Houston, Texas), 1953, 1960
  - U.S. Military Academy. (West Point, New York), 1958
  - U.S. Study Commission, Southeast River Basins (Columbus, Georgia), 1960
  - U.S. Treasury Department (San Francisco, California), 1955
  - U.S. War Department. The Adjutant General (Washington, D.C.), 1947
  - Upper Chattahooches Development Association (Buford, Georgia), 1960
  - Valley, Donald F. (Detroit, Michigan), 1958 (Box 8.)
  - Vandiver, Governor S. Ernest (Atlanta, Georgia), 1960
  - Van Houten, Major General John J. (Fort Carson, Colorado), 1955
  - Van Natta, Major General, 1957-1958
  - Vantine, Glenn (Bismarck, North Dakota), 1950
  - Van Wagoner, Brigadier General Lou G. (Washington, D.C.), 1957
  - Vaugham, Otis (Fort Sam Houston, Texas), 1950
  - Venable, Colonel Russell (Bowman, California), 1955
  - Veterans' Bureau (Washington, D.C.), 1954
  - Vigneras, M., 1953
  - Villines, Wilburn (Orange, California), 1955
  - Viney, Major General Alvin C., 1954-1960
  - Vining, Seth M. (Tryon, North Carolina), 1946, 1956, 1960
  - Vogel, Brigadier General Herbert D. (Knoxville, Tennessee), 1958-1960
  - Walsh, Richard S., Jr. (Atlanta, Georgia), 1960
  - Walton, Colonel Henry L. (Brussels, Belgium), 1958
  - Warner, Jack W., 1957-1958, 1960
  - Warner, Brigadier General L. V., 1954
  - Warrior-Tombigbee Development Association, The (Atlanta, Georgia), 1960
  - Washbourne Colonel Lee B. (Washington, D.C.), 1948
  - Watson, George (San Antonio, Texas), 1947
  - Weaver, Major Leslie F., 1947
  - Weaver, Brigadier General Miles (Washington, D.C.), 1947
  - Weaver, Colonel Theron D., 1952
  - Wedeman, John D. (Fort Sam Houston, Texas), 1950
  - Weible, Lieutenant General Walter L. (Washington, D.C.), 1956
  - Weinert, Colonel McD. D. (Ancon, Canal Zone), 1949
  - Weinstein, Major Lewis H., 1944
  - Weis, Nancy (Mrs. Donald R.) (Lake Stevens, Washington), 1959
  - Weiskopf, Mr. A. A. (Mobile, Alabama), 1960
  - Wells, Colonel Lucian (West Hyattsville, Maryland), 1955
  - Wescott, James R., Jr. (Washington, D.C.), 1956
  - West, Herbert G. (Walla Walla, Washington), 1959
  - Westmoreland, Major General William C., 1957, 1961
  - Westphalinger, Major General Henry R., 1957
  - Weyland, General O. P., 1956
  - Weyment, 1st Lieutenant H. S. (Langley Air Force Base, Virginia), 1955
  - Weyrauch, Brigadier General Paul R. (Fort Stewart, Georgia), 1957
  - Wheeler, Lieutenant General R. A. (Washington, D.C.), 1948, 1956
  - White, Brigadier General Charles H., Jr. (Fort Benning, Georgia), 1960
  - White, Brigadier General M. S. (Langley Air Force Base, Virginia), 1956
  - Whitlock, Francis B. (New York, New York), 1958
  - Whitmore, Lieutenant Colonel Morris T., 1943
  - Whitten, Lieutenant Colonel Frederick E., 1945
  - Wilcox, Donald B. (Gainsville, Florida), 1957, 1959-1960
  - Wilhide, Paul, 1956-1958
  - Will, Rear Admiral J. M. (Brooklyn, New York), 1961
  - Williams, D. Leon, 1960
  - Williams, Lieutenant General Edward T., 1952-1959
  - Williams, Rear Admiral Richard C. (Atlanta, Georgia), 1958
  - Wilson, Colonel John L., Jr. (Rock Island, Illinois), 1955
  - Wilson, Colonel Maybin H. (Austin, Texas), 1948
  - Wilson, Colonel N. B. (West Point, New York), 1959
  - Wilson, Major General W. K., Jr., 1954, 1960
  - Wirtz, Joseph M. (New Castle, Pennsylvania), 1956
  - Wood, Frank B. (Lincoln, Alabama), 1959
  - Wood, Brigadier General J. E., 1948, 1953
  - Wood, Milton L. (Atlanta, Georgia), 1957
  - Woodruff, James W. (Columbus, Georgia) 1958, 1960
  - Wozney, Colonel Michael J. (Forest Park, Georgia), 1959
  - Wright, R. P. (Indianapolis, Indiana), 1955
  - Yates, Lieutenant General Donald N. (Washington, D.C.), 1960
  - Yoder, Colonel Leverett G. (St. Paul, Minnesota), 1950
  - York, Lieutenant Commander J. "T", 1958
  - Young, James R. (Anderson, South Carolina), 1957-1959
  - Young, Brigadier General Mason J., 1947, 1952
  - Young, Senator Milton R. (Washington, D.C.), 1951
  - Young, Major General Robert N. (Washington, D.C.), 1954
  - Yount, Major General Paul F. (Washington, D.C.), 1956-1957
  - Zimmerman, Colonel George J. (Washington, D.C.), 1953
- Speeches and Writings, 1946-1959. (Box No. 8.)
  Arranged alphabetically by title or subject.
  - Titled speeches and writings (Box 8.)
    - "Beach Preservation Problems and Projects of the South Atlantic Division, Except for Florida." Speech, American Shore and Beach Preservation Association, Sarasota, Florida, April 16, 1959. Typewritten, 12 pages
    - "The End of the German Army." A request for review of the article, but the article itself is not present in the collection, 1946
    - "The Future Job for Engineers." Address, The Society of American Military Engineers meeting, Atlanta, Georgia, October 8, 1959. Typewritten, 22 pages
    - "Recent Trip to Europe." Talk to Atlanta General Depot Officers, n.p., Setember 26, 1958. Typewritten, 11 pages
    - "Super Project in North Dakota: the Garrison Dam and Reservoir." n.d. Typewritten, 16 pages.
  - Untitled speeches
    - Armed Forces Day Luncheon, Rome, Georgia, May 17, 1959. Typewritten, 7 pages.
    - Celebration of the 184th Anniversary of the Army Corps of Engineers, Atlanta, Georgia, June 12, 1959. Typewritten, 6 pages
    - Mid-Continent Development Council, Bismarck, North Dakota, September 6, 1950. Typewritten, 28 pages
    - Rotary Club, Bismarck, North Dakota, September 13, 1950. Typewritten, 12 pages.
    - Society of American Military Engineers meetings, Jacksonville, Florida, November 23, 1959. Typewritten, 22 pages
    - Warrior Lock and Dam Dedication near Eutaw, Alabama, October 16, 1958. Typewritten, 2 pages
    - Warrior-Tombigbee Development Association, Annual meeting, Tuscaloosa, Alabama, January 24, 1958. Typewritten, 10 pages
    - West Point Dinner Talk, Fort McPherson, March 14, 1958. Typewritten, 10 pages
- Subject File, 1944-1956. (Box No. 8.)
  Correspondence, notes, recommendations, printed matter, etc., arranged alphabetically by either author, title, or subject.
  - Albrecht, Page (Mrs. Frank M.), 1954 (Box 8.)
  - Allied Control Authority Military Directorate. 7th Meeting. Minutes. Berlin, October 6, 1945
  - Bonfiglio, Private James Sebastian. "To whom it may concern," 1944
  - Facts for the Family - Your son in the Army. 1954. Printed, 14 pages.
  - Grenoble, Universite de. Comte de Patronage des Etudiants Etrangers. Cours de Vacances. 57e Annee, Annee 1953
  - Pommier, Henriette. "To whom it may concern," 1953.
  - Sturgis, Major General Sam D., Jr., n.d.
  - Turner, Viola (Mrs.), (Hampton, Virginia), "To whom it may concern," 1956.
  - WAC Detatchment, Press Representatives (France), n.d.
  - Whitaker, Corporal Claud W. "To whom it may concern," 1944